Guide to the James R. Houck papers.
Houck, James R. papers.
- Series VII. IRAS (Infrared Astronomy Satellite)
  - NASA SIRTF Technology Readiness Review, 1982-02-03-1982-02-05 (Box 29)
  - SIRTF Free Flyer Phase A System Concept Description, 1984-05-03 (Box 29)
  - SELDADS(?) Program Documentation, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Series VIII. Jim Houck's Lear and C-141 Data
  - Computer Program Documentation, 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Computer Program Documentation, 1979-1981 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Computer Program Documentation, 1975-04-1976-05 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - C-141, E01, andE03 Reports, 1975-1977 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - A30, Line Ops, Phasing, and Cabin Cal Reports, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - C141 Charts and Printer Records, 1976-11 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - C141, Jupiter, PZ Cas, Ori M-82, UA3 Charts and Flight Plans, 1976-11 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - C-141 'Garbage' (H-sight data, optical specs, etc), 1975 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Spectral Averages Documentation, 1976-05 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Cabin Calculations, 1981-08-23 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - C-141 JRH, DFS, RAR, and WJF (?), 1975-04-01-1975-04-02 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Edited Spectra Documentation, 1976-11 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - C-141, IRC+10420, RX1300, PZ Cas, UofA 19, Mu Cep (?), 1977-06-21-1977-06-22 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Reduced Spectra Documentation, 1976-11 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - C-141 Flight Raw, real-time data, 1976-05-20-1976-05-21 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - C-141 Series Charts and Monsanto, 1976-05 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    RxBoo, M82, IRC+10420, UofA19, N6C 7027
  - Lear Chart and Printer Records, 1976-01 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Lear Jet Charts, 1976-10-1976-11 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Lear Jet Reduced Data (Graphs), 1976-01 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Small Dewar (Graphs), Undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Lear Flight Documentation, Mars and Moon, 1975-11-11-1975-11-12 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Lab Tests and Flight Series, 1979-06-1979-07 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Lear Data: Moon, Mars, Jupiter, Venus, 1975-06 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    Includes online C-141 pre+post flight spectra
  - Edited Spectra Documentation, 1976-05-18-1976-05-21 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Lear Data Reduced: Mars, Moon, Jupiter, Venus, 1975-06-1976-01 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Test Spectra, Flight Spectra, and Flight Plans, 1976-01 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Lear Jet (Raw Counts, Flight Plans, Log, Offsets), 1976-10-1976-11 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Lear and C-141 Line Fits Documentation, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - C-141 Navigation, 1974-09 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous C-141 and Lear Documentation, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous C-141 and Lear Documentation, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Spectrum Detectors, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Leaks and Ray Traces Documentation, Undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Ray Trace Results, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Blueprints, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Digital Tracker Flight Test Results, 1975 (Box 30)
  - Memoranda and Proposals, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - C-141 Flight Data, 1979-07-16-1979-07-17 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - C-141 Flight Data, 1979-07-18-1979-07-19 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    Rx Boo, NGC 6210, G45.1+0.1, IRC+10420, S158, W49, W3, Moon
  - Miscellaneous C-141 and Lear Documentation, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    IRC+10420, G29.9-0.0, K3-50, m8, W33, s Ceph, NGC 6884, G75.84+0.4
  - Miscellaneous C-141 and Lear Documentation, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous C-141 and Lear Documentation, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Lear Jet Flight Chart Records, 1977-09-1977-10 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    C-141, Ori, +10216, Callish/Gary, (illegible), CRL 618, VCVn, AZ Uma, N6C2392
  - Monsanto Tapes and Lear Jet Flights, 1977-09-1977-10 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence with Bill Forrest, Undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - C-141 Documentation Houck/McCarthy/Forrest, 1978-01-05-1978-01-06 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - C-141 Edited Data, 1979-07 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    uCep, Rcas, NGC 1068, M82, Mars, NML Tau, Titan
  - Hawaii Adventure, 1977-04-1977-05 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - NASA AMES MOFFETT Test Spectra, 1978-01-03 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - C-141 Edits, 1978-01 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Raw Data from Lear Jet (Moon, Venus, Mars, Mock Lear (postflight and preflight)), 1978-07-1978-08 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    Note: "All look ok on strip chart- leave"
- Series IX. Gemini Telescope
  - Gemini Telescopes NSF Independent Review Committee, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Gemini 8-M Telescopes Project, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Gemini Board Meeting Materials, 1994-05-23-1994-05-24 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Gemini Telescope Manuals, Undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Gemini Telescope AURA (Association of Universities for Research in Astronomy) Records, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Gemini Board Meeting Materials, 1994-05-23-1994-05-24 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Gemini-Related Correspondence, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Newsletters, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Gemini Proposals, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Mauna Kea Site Construction, 1995-01-15 (Box 34)
  - Documents Regarding Gemini Construction, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Gemini Reports, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Gemini Correspondence, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Gemini: 1-5 Spectrograph Proposal Review, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Gemini Board Meeting Materials, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Gemini/NOAO Newsletters, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Gemini Board Meeting Materials, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Infrared Astronomy Panel Papers, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Gemini Preliminary Design Review, 1992-12-09 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Gemini Board Meeting Materials, 1992-11-09-1992-11-11 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Gemini Materials, 1992-11-09-1992-11-11 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Requests for Proposal- Gemini, 1992-05-06 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Gemini Materials, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Gemini Materials, 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Misc. Gemini Materials, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Misc. Gemini Materials, 1991-1993 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Misc. Gemini Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Misc. Gemini Presentations, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Gemini Design Review, 1992-12-09 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Misc. Gemini Materials, 1991-1993 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Misc. Gemini Materials, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Gemini Projection, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Budget Proposals, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Gemini Review, 1991-1993 (Box 39, Folder 17)